<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CyberFortress</title>
    <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CyberFortress</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 13:42:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.cyberfortress.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 13:42:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/</guid>
      <description>CyberFortress is an insuretech MGA based in San Antonio, TX.
We&#39;re building a new kind of online business interruption policy designed for small business.
Narrowly-focused and parametric in nature, this policy will begin paying out within 24 hours of a cyber incident - providing valuable cash-on-hand to help our customers weather the immediate storm.
To do this, we&#39;re also building a new way to model online cyber risk.
We&#39;re building a machine that continuously collects the evidence of technology choices ecommerce businesses make - thousands of features per domain - and makes sense of this noise via machine learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licenses</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/licenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 13:42:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/licenses/</guid>
      <description> CyberFortress Insurance Services US, LLC is a licensed insurance producer in the following states.
We&#39;re in the process of getting licenses in all 50 states -- if your state isn&#39;t listed, please check back soon.   State General Lines # Surplus Lines #     TX 2368785 2376542     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Developer</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/full-stack-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 15:50:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/full-stack-developer/</guid>
      <description> We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a full-stack web applications developer to help build a new kind of cyber claims management system from scratch: one that leverages automation to deliver the fastest-possible payout of standard claims!
Requirements  3+ years working as a developer on interactive applications - preferably in a small or startup environment Strong expertise in web development with technologies like Express, Flask, Ruby on Rails, Angular, and React A believable perspective on application security A fast learner, a fast prototyper, ability to work independently Familiar with relational and NoSQL cloud datastores Familiar with the Google Cloud Platform  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Underwriter</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/underwriter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 13:15:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/underwriter/</guid>
      <description> We are looking for an imaginative and rigorous underwriter who is excited to work with our technology and insurance operations teams to take on the most significant business risk of the 21st century: cyber.
Requirements  Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree and 3+ years of related insurance experience; or equivalent combination of education and experience Advanced professional insurance coursework (i.e., CPCU, ASLI, and AU) or completion of other insurance-related classes is necessary.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actuary</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/actuary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 13:11:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/actuary/</guid>
      <description> We are looking for a creative, thoughtful actuary who wants to work with our technology team to understand, evaluate, and price the most significant business risk of the 21st century: cyber.
Requirements  Demonstrated experience and training as an actuary Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or higher in mathematics, or actuarial science Coursework in statistics, economics, computer science, calculus, and corporate finance beneficial Associate- or fellow-level certification with either the Casualty Actuarial Society / CAS (for actuaries interested in the property and casualty field) in good standing  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Developer</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/systems-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 12:09:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/systems-developer/</guid>
      <description> We&amp;rsquo;re looking for an accomplished API and systems developer to help us collect, store, and serve massive amounts data from the internet. Sound fun?
Requirements  3+ years working as a technical architect or systems developer - preferably in a small or startup environment Strong background in API design, development, distributed systems, and datastores A Believable perspective on application security A fast learner, a fast prototyper, ability to work independently Familiar with the Google Cloud Platform  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Designer</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/ux-designer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 11:46:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/ux-designer/</guid>
      <description> We are looking for a UX designer to be a part of the product team focused on transforming one of the most hated consumer experiences in the world, insurance buying, into one of the most delightful consumer experiences in the world.
Requirements  At least 1 year in product design or UX Fluency in standard UX software Willingness to take risks A priority on elegance in design Imagination  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/data-scientist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 10:49:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/careers/data-scientist/</guid>
      <description> We&amp;rsquo;re looking for a data scientist to help us build the world a better model for cyber risk. If you love ML, solving huge problems, and are an experienced data scientist; you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place!
Requirements  3+ years working as a data scientist Strong background in machine learning, computer science, statistics, and maths Works in Python Loves its numpy, pandas, matplotlib, scikit-learn, and keras packages A fast learner, a builder Familiar with relational and NoSQL cloud datastores Familiar with the Google Cloud Platform  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Culture Blueprint</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 20:14:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/culture/</guid>
      <description>CyberFortress was formed to be a new kind of company to tackle a big problem. Insurance is one of the most painful and hated experiences in modern life. We want to change that. But we don’t think we can change the insurance industry without first changing ourselves. So we have thrown out a lot of the startup playbook: No founder dictators. No managers. No vesting handcuffs. No work obsession leading to burnout.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/tos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 15:45:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/tos/</guid>
      <description>These Terms of Service (hereinafter the &amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) are a legal agreement between you and Porthcawl Insurance Services US, LLC d/b/a CyberFortress (referred to in the Terms as &amp;ldquo;CyberFortress&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;we&amp;rdquo;, us&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;).
IT IS VERY IMPORTANT THAT YOU READ THESE TERM VERY CAREFULLY AS THEY CONSTITUTE A BINDING LEGAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND US, AND THEY STATE THE AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND US REGARDING EACH OF OUR LEGAL RIGHTS, REMEDIES AND OBLIGATIONS TO THE OTHER PARTY.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 22:11:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Porthcawl Insurance Services US, Inc. d/b/a CyberFortress and its affiliates (&amp;ldquo;CyberFortress”, we&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;our company&amp;rdquo;) take the privacy of our customers and other visitors to our website (&amp;ldquo;you&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;your&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;your company&amp;rdquo;) seriously. Because we value our customer relationships, we do not sell customer information. We will only share your information for the purposes of providing services which you have engaged us to perform on your behalf, such as placing your insurance, and/or providing you with insurance-related products or services, as applicable, and as otherwise permitted or required by law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Team</title>
      <link>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/the-cyberfortress-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 19:53:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.cyberfortress.com/about/the-cyberfortress-team/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>